ROSEMARY MATILIEWS





ABOUT

I am a 4th year student at the University of Florida with a full academic merit scholarship. I expect to graduate in summer 2023 and receive my Bachelor of Fine Arts degree with an emphasis in painting as well as a graphic design certificate. I am driven and passionate about the arts, with proficient skills in Adobe Suite as well as excellent research and writing capabilities and knowledge of digital media, advertising, art history, and contemporary art.

EDUCATION

University of Florida, c/o 2023

- -B.F.A in painting
- -Certificate in Graphic Design
- -Florida Bright Futures scholar
- -3.75 G.P.A.

SKILLS

Technical Skills:

- -Adobe Suite- particularly Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, & XD
- -Painting- oil, acrylic, and watercolor
- -Drawing/Illustration
- -Printmaking-silkscreen, intaglio, and relief
- -Customer Service
- -Color Theory
- -Ceramics- throwing and handbuilding
- -Woodworking & operation of power tools

Soft Skills:

- -Problem solving
- -Attention to detail
- -Time management
- -Team player

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern, Moisturizer Art Gallery; Gainesville, FL — 2022-present

- -Represented the gallery at Miami Art Week 2022, assisted with their exhibition "We Don't Respect Borders: Meditations on Abjection and the Femme Body" at Satellite Art Fair
- -Other responsibilities include setting up gallery spaces, working gallery events, reaching out to artists, conducting research, etc.

Graphics and Layout Designer, Gelée Magazine; Gainesville, FL — 2020-2022

- -Member of the graphics and layout team for a student-run art magazine based in Gamesville
- -Responsible for designing graphics for the Instagram account, spreads for the publication, and some brand merchanidising
- -Furthered my abilities in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and Indesign
- -Taught me the importance of meeting deadlines, editing, and being detail-oriented

Art Captain and Coordinator, Project Makeover; Gainesville, FL — 2019-2021

- -Worked for Project Makeover for two years, a UF-affiliated club that works on the beautification of local elementary and middle schools
- Served as captain first year and coordinator second year for the art team, helping to design and paint large-scale murals at multiple schools
- -Learned valuable team leadership and organizing skills

Depop Online Store Owner; Tampa, FL — 2019-present

- -Curate unique and vintage thrift store finds, as well as model and photograph them myself
- -Became a Depop Featured Seller and amassed over 2,000 followers

